How much do you get
Ты сколько получаешь
paid, what is five 5000 dollars if in
зарплату что пять 5000 долларов если на
dollars per month
доллары в месяц
Well, you want to say that you are in Russia
Да ну ты хочешь сказать что ты в России
Izhevsk you get half a million rubles per
ижевски получаешь полмиллиона рублей в
month great hello where are you from guys
месяц здорово привет Вы откуда пацанчики
sska Russia
сска Россия
Udmurtia varnish my father is from Zhav Mom is from
Удмуртия лак у меня отец из жав Мама из
Votkinsk I am Udmurt and
Воткинска я удмурт а
Vyre are you Russian or Udmurt
выре вы русские или
I don’t know as if Russian
удмурты я не знаю как будто бы
Well, I am Udmurt I don’t know Well are you
русский Ну я удмуртский не знаю Ну вы
Russian or Udmurt Well I was born in
русский или удмурты Ну я родился в
Zhev by nationality who are you Russian Let it
жев по национальности кто Ты русский
be so
Пусть будет так
understood America from behind Well I live in America and
понял Америки сзади Ну в Америке живу и
what is
что
lira in Russia Well, parents Yes they
лир в России Ну родители Да они сейчас в
live in Udmurtia now And what did you decide to move
удмурти живут А ты что решил переехать
Well, 18 years ago I went to America to
Ну я 18 лет назад поехал в Америку
study and stayed there I really liked it here
учиться и там остался реально тут
I compared Izhevsk and
сравнил ижаев и
California come on name
Калифорнию давай назви
me at least
мнем хотя бы
when I need to live in Izhevsk not This is a difficult
при надо жить в Ижевске не Это сложный
question just Name three reasons why yes
вопрос просто Назови три причины почему
three reasons why to live in
ть да три причины почему жить в
California
Калифорнии
climate salaries so infrastructure Well,
климат зарплаты так инфраструктура Ну
infrastructure No come on another what not
инфраструктура Нет давай другою что нет
And what  infrastructure than well than everything
А чем инфраструктура чем ну чем всё у
we have in short damn roads airports schools
нас короче блин дороги аэропорты школы
hospitals like whatever you want I sat down in a van in
больницы типа что хочешь Я ван сел
short in
короче
short 3 hours in Hawaii sat in short
через короче 3 часа на Гаваях сел короче
3 hours in the Maldives
3 часа на Мальдивах
in general I know Chebureki dumplings and uh it's
вобще зна Чебуреки пельмени и
obvious that dumplings and
э видно что пельмени и
chebureki No well like this is the climate of the market
чебуреки Не ну как бы это климат базара
But it's like for
Но это как
someone who loves linden
бы тому ктолюбит плы липу
how much 12 I like it like this And for
сколько 12 мне это мне нравится такая А
someone who always gets a plus Well like
кому постоянно плюс кайф Ну как бы
Bazaar zero everyone has their own I understood Well okay
Базара ноль у каждого своё понял Ну
Yes interesting And so really you were
хорошо Да интересно А так-то реально ты
also born in Udmurtia in Izhevsk there is no here it is
родился тоже в Удмуртии в Ижевске нет
Yes I was born in my passport it
вот он Да я родился у меня в паспорте
says uh not in the passport but in the
написано ээ не в паспорте а в
birth certificate there is also such a green
свидетельстве рождения ещё такое зелёное
Soviet one it says Udmurt ASSR and
Советское там написано Удмуртская АССР а
how old are you 43 years old I was
а тебе сколько лет 43 года я восемьдесят
born in the eighty-first year you look good
первого года рождения у хорошо выглядишь
not just like dumplings not a beetle
не просто как пельмени не жука
bro m Tes in America your
братуха м Тесь в Америке своей
California Coca-Cola you eat
Калифорнии кока-кола питаетесь
Coca-Cola you eat It can't be Well
кока-кола питаетесь Не может быть Ну
look you have
смотри у вас есть
something like that  Russians' opinion of us is that we
такое россиян мнение о нас что мы тут
drink Coca-Cola and eat burgers here, but
пьём кока-колу и едим бургеры только не
that's not it, there's quite a
то есть тут довольно
wide selection of products in Russia, do
обширная выбор продуктов в России
n't tell me how many options you have for
столько не свети сколько ты вариан
sausages in Russia, you
колбас в России
know Well, you know, there are a lot of options, but it's
знаешь Ну знаешь вариантов много но как
like the ones you eat are like
будто бы те которые ты кушаешь это ну
units, let's say, boiled, smoked, Well,
единиц условно допустим там варёная
something like that, and I remember what sausage is
что-то типа и я помню что такое колбаса
in Russia, it's some kind of, in short, mixed with
в России это какая-то короче смешанной
paper, some kind of incomprehensible cartilage, and
бумагой непонятные какие-то хрящами и
so on,
так дальше
ground, which was in
перемолотый что был в
Russia 18 years
Росси 18 лет
ago, everything changed here dramatically Yes,
назад тут всё поменялось кардинально Да
of course, everything is changing everywhere My
конечно всё всюду всё меняется У меня
parents live with me In short, I send
родители живут Короче я маме присылаю
money to my mother, I help, I see what kind of
деньги помогаю я вижу что там за
horror there is So what, what kind of horror, I have some kind of
жесть Так что а что что за жесть у меня
friends living in Votkinsk, like, well,
вот живут как бы кенты в воткинские типа
at my mother's, look, if my mother, uh, worked as a
ну у мамы смотри если мама ээ работала
nurse all her life and receives a pension of
всю жизнь медсестрой и получает пенсию
18,600 rubles, which is what doctors receive little in
18600 руб что врачи получают мало в
Russia I completely agree with you,
Росии Я с тобой полностью
everything mm,
согласен всё мм
and to come to America to get sick or  a common
а приехать в Америку заболеть or обычной
cold
простудой
and or I don't remember what an acute respiratory
и or не пом что острое респираторное
disease cough sniffles Well, a common
заболевание кашель соп Ну тако обычная
cold, so to speak, and get sick with it in
простуда так скажем и заболеть этим в
America I don't know how many thousands of
Америке Я не знаю сколько ты тысяч
dollars you'll give to get you in the hospital
долларов отдашь чтобы тебя поле в больни
Well, I had covid I had covid
сколько Ну вот ковид был я болел ковидом
And where are you sick with
А где ты боле
covid California
ковидом Калифорнии
that you also had covid Are you
что ковид у вас тоже был Ты что
kidding me it was in all countries not
прикалываешься он во всех странах был не
only Izhevsk In short, as if it
только ижевски Короче как будто бы он
affected Russia the most
Россию больше всех затронул
not only in Izhevsk in China where they ate in
не только в Ижевский в Китае где сожрали
short this bat Well, it was it was
короче эту мышу летучую Ну это же было
n't a disease It was
это же была не болячка Это же было
overpopulation of the
перенаселение
country of countries in the sense of overpopulation Well,
страны стран в смысле перенаселение Ну
how all the elderly people in the hospital
как всех всех пожилых людей в больнице
it's a fact I didn't understand what happened to you there I do
это же факт Не понял что у вас там
n't understand Well, let's say I'll
случилось не понимаю Ну допустим я тебе
tell you from my own example I had a
на своём примере скажу у меня была
great-grandmother she lived in such an area in
прабабушка она жила в таком районе в
Izhevsk the area was I don't know maybe you
Ижевске район был я не знаю может ты
probably don't remember since 20 years
наверное уже не помнишь раз там 20 лет
ago I came there there was a Tatar bazaar area this is
назад приехал был район татар базар это
where there were only private sectors that is,
где были только частные секторы то есть
all the grandmothers there knew each other still  since the
там все бабушки друг друга знали ещё со
Great Patriotic War, so to
времён там Великий отечественный войны
speak, She
условно так скажем Она дальше своего
never went anywhere beyond her garden house, fell
огорода домика никуда не выходила
ill with
заболела
Covid, everything was Good hop, they took her to the
ковидом всё было Гуд хоп отвезли в
hospital, she was on the mend, her condition
больницу пошла на поправку состояние
improved, it was a day off,
улучшилось был выходной день пришла
some
какая-то
nurse came and left her an injection, the next
медсестра оставила ей укол на следующий
day her grandmother
день бабушка
died,
умерла
and not with the disabled, but with the elderly. I have
и не с инвалидами А с пожилыми Я очень
heard a lot of such cases,
много таких случаев слышал очень
many people need to pay pensions,
многому нужно выплачивать пенсию
especially to veterans of the Great Patriotic
особенно ветеранам Великой Отечественной
War. That is, do I understand correctly that you
войны То есть я правильно понимаю что ты
want to say that Putin really
хочешь сказать что Путин реально через
killed these pensioners through Covid, this is what the whole
ковид поубивал этих пенсионеров это весь
world does, as if, well, in your Russia,
мир делае как будто бы ну у вас в России
Putin did it, yes. Well, I
Путин это сделал получается да Ну я не
will not be so harsh about this topic.
буду так жёстко заявлять об этой теме
I just know this fact and, as if what
Просто я знаю этот факт и как бы что
really happened, I don’t know. Well, wait.
было на самом деле я не знаю ну подожди
Well, the fact is that in Russia, the
ну факт в том что у вас в России
government has pensioners through Covid, just
пенсионеров власть через ковид просто
Pooh something
Поу нечто
[music]
[музыка]
I am speaking personally for my grandmother about yes, that
Я говорю лично за свою бабушку про да то
is, your grandmother was killed by the state
есть твою бабушку убило государство
so as not to pay her a pension. I
чтобы не выплачивать ей пенсию я
heard correctly. I don’t know how to tell you exactly about this,
Услышал я не знаю как тебе точно об этом
I will not directly  to beat on your
сказать я не буду прямо лупить на твой
question yes or no I just gave you a
вопрос да или нет Я тебе просто привёл
statement of
констатации
facts Let me now about I am stating a
фактов Давай я сейчас про Констатирую
fact It seems to me that you felt
факт Мне кажется ты почувствовал у себя
inside yourself It is not your inner core
внутри Это не твой внутренний стержень
now yes it is the FSB getting in Yes I did
сейчас есть да это ФСБ пробирается
not understand you Well that is what you as a
Да не понял тебя Ну вот то что ты как
man Yes every man feels an
мужчина Да каждый мужчина ощущает себе
inner core yes And you now realized
внутренний стержень да А ты сейчас понял
that it is not the inner core of
что это не внутренний стержень это
comrade major
товарища майора У
You do not disagree with you I do not agree you are
тебя не не согласен с тобой не согласен
just afraid what are you afraid of the
просто боишься чего боишься
question
вопрос
why did the authorities kill your grandmother
зачем власти убивать твою бабушку было
If her pension was already low Why
Если у неё и так низкая пенсия Почему
low She is a veteran of the Great
низко Она же ветеран Великой
Patriotic War and how much
Отечественной войны и сколько она
pension did she receive I do not
получала пенсию Я не
know Well I think in any case more than just a
знаю Ну я думаю всяко больше чем просто
pensioner
пенсионер
No I am
Нет я
wrong how do you feel about the fact that
ошибаюсь как относишься к тому что
now Russia is out with Ukraine and how I want
сейчас Россия выт с Украиной и как хочу
it all to end as soon as possible and that's it
чтобы это всё закончилось уже поскорее и
And why do you think it
всё А как думаешь почему она
started not
началось не
[music] I
[музыка]
know
знаю отмывание
money laundering and what do you think I think that
денег а ты как думаешь я думаю что
now Trump came and in
сейчас Трамп пришёл и в
Russia that Trump came to Russia yes what will happen what will happen that
России то что Трамп пришёл России да что
he has already declared to us
что будет та что он уже у нас заявил вам
I am watching Russian  television yes Here
Я вот смотрю Российское телевидение да
in America you stupidly show
Вот и у нас в Америке у вас тупо речи
Trump's speeches some of which are
трампа показывают некоторые которые
beneficial to Russia we have what shows He
выгодно России у нас что показы Он
says He made an ultimatum to Putin
говорит Он же сделал Ультиматум Путину
in 90 days to withdraw troops from Ukraine
за 90 дней вывести войска из Украины
otherwise he says it will be worse otherwise like he
иначе говорит будет хуже иначе типа он
gives all
даёт всю
power or what not sanctions Of course yes But
мощь или что не санкции Само собой да А
this is how he gives Ukraine a full line
вот так он даёт Украине полную линейку
with permission to hit the Russian Federation at any depth
с разрешением бить на любую глубину
Look, you have
Российской Федерации Вот смотри у вас же
already flown drones to Izhevsk
уже в Ижевск долетали дроны
really Vokin dole Yes this is all
правда Вокин доле Да это всё
American ours it's not Ukrainians I do
американский наш это ж не украинцы делаю
understand this is not Ukraine these are ours
понима это ж не Украин это наши
American
американский
Drone How can you say ours Parents
Дрон Как ты можешь говорить наши Родите
live in Russia I am 18 years old I am an
живут в Росси я 18 лет Я гражданин
American citizen SST
Америки сст
permanent citizenship citizenship I
постоянно гражданство гражданство Я
received
получил
citizenship And do you
гражданство А ты английский прям в
know English perfectly or are you just
совершенстве знаешь или ты просто
perfect Yes I teach at a
совершенстве Да я преподаю в
university
университете
and listen to the accent Do you want to
а акцент послушать Ты меня хочешь
check me Let's first you
Проверить хочу Давай ты сначала ска до
count to 20 I will tell you you have British
20 считаю я тебе скажу у тебя Бритиш
orlish Let me count fre And you
илиш Давай я буду считать fre А ты
will Yes in short with this you are in America in
будешь Да вот короче с этим ты в Америке
short you will be
короче будеь
Okay I don't live in America  20 years I
Окей я не живу в Америке 20 лет тебя
want to
хочу
hear you are you a baby want to test me
услышать ты малыш хочешь меня проверять
I want to hear
Я хочу услышать акцент
your accent Well it's not difficult for you like if I knew
твой Ну тебе же не сложно типа знал бы я
another language I would be with you just why Yes
другой язык я бы с тобой просто зачем Да
I'm just interested And why do I need this
просто мне интересно А мне зачем это
just tell me a phrase in
просто скажи мне фразу на английском
English Why not
языке Зачем не
this in the sense why okay phrase come on
это в смысле зачем хорошо фразу давай
what does it mean You should
что это означает Ты по-любому должен
know anyway if you have at least B2 language
знать если ты хотя бы B2 имеешь язык ещё
again Ball Hada is a proverb in
раз Болл Хада это поговорка на
English there is
английском
no such thing I don't know bowl bowl
языке нет такого я не знаю
Well shar
боул Ну шар
shar shar is
шар шар - это
bol it's bowl and
бол это боул а
what does a bowl mean And what does this phrase mean I
как миска будет А что значит эта фраза Я
say what a bowl will be
говорю как миска будет
in English
по-английски
like mi from which they eat a
как ми из которой едят
bowl and what did you want me to say in
миска а что ты хотел меня
English you will understand the accent if you
по-английски ты акцент разберёшь если ты
don't understand the word in order to
не понимаешь слова для того чтобы акцент
understand the accent you need all this but what do you know a
понять нужно это всё но что знаешь тебе
Caucasian will tell you Gru and a pear you will understand
кавказец скажет Грю и груша ты поймёшь
if the word pear You know how it sounds yes
если слово груша Ты знаешь как звучит да
And if he tells you sha Listen and such a
А если он скажет тебе ша Слушай а такой
question And why did you come to America 20
вопрос А почему ты приехал в Америку 20
years ago and didn't move your parents
лет назад и не перевёз сво к родителя
what what and parents don't want mom  doesn't
что что а родители не хотят мама не
want I don't believe mom doesn't want No she
хочет не верю мама не хочет Нет она
said I was born here I will live here
говорила я тут родилась я тут буду жить
like well and so what do you have mom is such a
типа ну и что то есть у тея мама такой
temperament I was born here I t Well that's it Well that's what they are
закал я тут родилась я т
Soviet people
Ну вот Ну вот такие они советские люди
are like yeah And what are you doing here You won't
есть да И что здесь делаешь Ты же не
bring her by force And what
Привезёшь её насильно А что тебя что
pushed you that you I got a student visa
пододвинул я получил студенческую визу
to study there uh at the University of
чтобы поучиться там э в университете
Sacramento study stayed for graduate school
Сакраменто поучи остался на аспирантуру
submitted documents And then if you give
подал документы А дальше если ты даёшь
graduate school they give you a residence permit oh and
аспирантуру тебе дают видно жительство о
if you defend your dissertation then they give
и если защищаешь диссертацию тогда дают
citizenship under a simplified procedure I
гражданство по упрощённой процедуре я
defended my dissertation and I teach at the
защитил диссертацию да и преподаю в
university citizenship that
университе гражданство что гражданство
you get citizenship yes yes 8 years ago I already
тебе получается да да 8 лет назад уже
received citizenship yeah And the fact that you are coming
получил гражданство да А то что ты
to Russia now, let's say, is you
сейчас в Россию допустим приедешь это ты
mine I will not come to Russia no if I
мо я не приеду в Россию нет если я
come because I will say so I was not
приеду потому что я скажем так меня не
recognized as an agent Yes but I will say
не признали ина агентом Да но я скажем
with us You are not a public person what why are you
снм Ты же не публич что что с чего тебя
recognized as an agent You are not some kind of
признают Ино агентом Ты же не какая-то
public person I am a member of the Republican
публичная я я член Республиканской
Party I  I am a member of the
партии я вхожу в городе Сакраменто в
city senate in Sacramento, I am an assistant to the senator and I have
сенат городской о помощник сенатора и я
publicly voiced quite unpleasant things
довольно неприятные вещи публично
against the Russian Federation
озвучивал против Российской Федерации
personally Putin yes that is well
лично Путина да то есть
therefore Well I will definitely not come to
ну поэтому Ну я я однозначно не приеду в
Russia while this regime exists I will not come
Россию пока этот режим есть я не приеду
I am helping to destroy this regime and
Я помогаю уничтожить этот режим а
coming is another matter
приехать коне другой вопрос родители у
your parents are still in Russia
тебя остались в России
so you are not going to
так не собираешься в
No as long as this whole situation continues
Нет пока эта вся ситуация продолжается
it can continue for 5 years 10 years 15
она может продолжаться 5 лет 10 лет 15
years you and your residents are already ready to
лет ты со своими жителями уже всё готов
never see each other again or what do you
больше никогда не видеться или что в
mean they can easily go to
смысле они спокойно могут выезжать в
Armenia to Kazakhstan For example
Армению в Казахстан Мы например ээ в
last year we met in Georgia
прошлом году в Грузии
I paid for their travel to
встречались я я им оплатил ээ дорогу в
Georgia they came to Georgia in Batumi
грузи они приехали в Грузию в Батуми
like we were in Adjara I flew in what is the
типа мы в аджаре были Я прилетел в чём
problem what does it mean on your T-shirt
проблема что у тебя на футболке означает
Well it is a Ukrainian trident My friends
Ну это тризуб украинский Это мои друзья
from Ukraine sent it to me And you have no friends
из Украины мне прислали А у тебя друзей
from Russia There are also friends from Russia yes
с России нету Есть и друзья из России да
And why don't you have a Russian coat of arms Well
А почему ты не с российским гербом Ну
they sent me a T-shirt
они мне прислали футболку
RDC What does it mean Russian
РДК Что это значит русский
volunteer corps these are ours  Russians
добровольческий корпус это наши россияне
who are fighting for Ukraine
которые воюют за Украину
against
против против
Putin's Denis Kapustin maybe you know them
путинской Денис Капустин може знаете их
Leader I do
Лидер
n't know Well you see you don't even know our
не знаю Ну вот видишь ты даже не знаешь
Russian heroes
русских героев
now look now our Russia has been
наших сейчас смотри сейчас нашу Россию
turned into some kind of circus Akhmat
превратили знаешь в какой-то цирк Ахмат
You can say our Russia Or you
Ты можешь говорить нашу Россию Или ты
just Look at least I am a citizen of
просто Смотри я хоть Я гражданин
Russia this America Yes USA But I
Российской этой Америки Да США Но я же
remained a citizen of the Russian Federation
остался гражданином Российской Федерации
I have two passports I did not renounce
У меня два паспорта Я же не отказывался
Russian citizenship Therefore yes
от российского гражданства Поэтому да
this is my Russia
это моя Россия
and if you had not moved to America then what
а если бы ты не Переезжал в Америку то
next Well what would have happened then if you had not
что дальше Ну что тогда было если бы не
moved to America most likely I would have been
Переезжал в Америку скорее всего меня бы
imprisoned like Navalny or even for
посадили как Навального или бы даже за
my
мою
activities there are you directly against Russia
деятельность есть ты прям против России
conditionally I am against the
условно Я против
Kremlin the
кремлёвской
Kremlin because they occupied Russia
кремл потому что они оккупировали Россию
this cooperative lakes look Russia
вот этот кооператив озера смотри Россия
has oil gas gold diamonds the richest
имеет нефть газ золото алмазы богатейшая
and why do they live poorly so explain people
а почему живут бедно так люди объясни
who live poorly you live poorly my
кто живёт бедно вы живёте бедно мои
parents live poorly everyone lives in Russia
родители живут бедно все живут в России
poorly And in your America everyone lives rich
бедно А у вас в Америке все богаты живут
and you have no I live VKh I explain
и у вас нет никакого Я живу ВХ объясняю
Look I am a university teacher
Смотри я Я преподаватель университета У
I have a salary of 99,000 dollars what do you
меня зарплата 99.000 долларов что ты мне
want to tell me about poor America that's
хочешь рассказать про Америку бедную вот
just with
просто у
us ru with We have 900,000 rubles
нас ру с У нас у нас 900.000 руб
in your opinion Yes per month Well almost a million
по-вашему Да в месяц Ну почти миллион
yes And this is
да И это небольшая
still small look at the salaries of teachers
ещё посмотри зарплаты преподавателей
America
Америка
California so you say that here they somehow
Калифорнии так говоришь что у нас как-то
live poorly or
живут бедно либо
in tents on the street a street full of
ет в палатках на улице полная улица
tents I explain why look Super
палаток объясняю почему так смотри Супер
you
вы мне
all tell me so much a good climate there are people to
все так много у хороший климат есть люди
live do you know why in Izhevsk there is
кое жить знаешь почему в Ижевске
no Because there is Winter because they
нет Потому что есть Зима потому что они
freeze
вымерзает
just freezes and that's it And with us yes with us
просто вымерзает и всё А у нас да у нас
if a person wants here they have khomus
если человек хочет вот они есть по хомус
Yes they have such a lifestyle the
Да вот у них такой стиль жизни им
state pays them 2,000 Well if to
государство выплачивают 2.000 Ну если
be exact 2300 2,300 dollars a month and
точно быть 2300 2.300 долларов в месяц и
they all live peacefully with us in
они все спокойно живут у нас в
California these are not like in Russia with us
Калифорнии это не те что в России у нас
they have hostels where they wash
они у них есть хостелы где они моются
specially yes like they live That is
специально да типа они живут То есть
just they live like this for them it's a joke like for
просто они вот живут им так в прикол как
them in short it's a joke like this to
вот например им короче в прикол типа вот
live like this  itu and everything is a free country
так жить так иту и всё свободная страна
there the temperature is such that you can
там температура такая что можно короче
live on the beach for a whole year in short he lives
целый год короче жить на пляже живёт ему
Cool But look how much do you
Прикольно А вот смотри ты сколько
get
получаешь
in dollars tell you Yes I'll
зарплату в долларах тебе говорить Да я
divide by 100 to get dollars in
разделю на 100 чтобы получить доллары в
whatever you want say
чём хочешь скажи
[music]
[музыка]
Well it's always different
Ну по-разному так всегда
Come on How much is p what five 5,000 dollars
Давай Сколько п что пять 5.000 долларов
if in dollars per month
если на доллары в месяц
Yes you want to say that you in Russia
Да ты хочешь сказать что ты в России
Izhevsk get half a million rubles per
ижевски получаешь полмиллиона рублей в
month
месяц рабо
officially I don't remember
официально не пом
really funny guy the average salary in
реально смешной тип средняя зарплата в
Izhevsk is about damn 30-40 ssia rubles sop
Ижевске порядка блин 30-40 сся рубле соп
But I don't work officially I'm a
Так я же не работаю официально я
designer designer and you get
дизайнер дизайнер и ты получаешь
half a million rubles Yeah right 400 I'm
полмиллиона рублей Да ну 400 Я же тебе
telling you plus or minus 300 500 300 500 Show me the
говорю плюс-минус 300 500 300 500 Покажи
account number on the card Show me just for
ка на карточке счёт Покажи вот ради
fun And you Show me yours all all the
интерес А ты Покажи мне свой всё всё
knowledge gave you a
знание дал чу
designer
дизайнер
5000 From your environment it's clear that you are a
5000 по твоей обстановке видно что ты
five-thousandth I'll show you how would you
пятитысячных я тебе покажу как бы ты
Show me yours what  te I explain Let's do it
Покажи мне свой что у те я объясни Давай
this way I'll just explain to you now why you
так я тебе просто сейчас объясню почему
what you
ты что ты
design project design of
дизайни дизайн проекта
houses design of private houses How much does
домов дизайн частный домов Сколько стоит
one project cost in the region of 1000 dollars
один проект в районе 1000 долларов
how much do you make them per month
сколько ты делаешь их в месяц
Cheche already 5.000 it doesn't work Well I
чече уже 5.000 не получается Ну тебе
told you plus or minus
сказал плюс-минус
so there is when seven when three per
так есть когда сем когда три в
month
месяц
piddip on my Telegram right now axis
пидпись на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось
win and
вин а
popk this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through Scar George in the shadows ban and very
нас через Скар Геор в теней бан и дуже
many videos I don't show to people at times I don't
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That's why
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
written right now and while there in Telegram there are
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
also interesting and useful
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry with you
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
constant operational links
постийний оперативный зв'язок
independently in that chi will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава украини пись
with
с